<tei xml:space="preserve">
    <teiHeader>
        <fileDesc xml:id="_0"/>
    </teiHeader>
    <text xml:lang="en">
        <listBibl>

        References<lb/> 
        <bibl>Abdo, A., Ackemann, M., Ajello, M., Allafort, A., Baldini, L., Balle, J., et al.: 2011, Gamma-ray flares from<lb/> the Crab Nebula. Science 331, 739.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Adams, W.M., Sturrock, P.A.: 1975, A model of coronal holes. Astrophys. J. 202, 259.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Aharanov, Y., Bohm, D.: 1959, Significance of electromagnetic potentials in the quantum theory. Phys. Rev.<lb/> 115, 485.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Alburger, D.E., Harbottle, G., Norton, E.F.: 1986, Half-life of 32 Si. Earth Planet. Sci. Lett. 78, 168.<lb/> Anderson, P.W.: 1990, On the nature of physical laws. Phys. Today 43(12), 9.<lb/> </bibl>
        P.A. Sturrock<lb/> 
        <bibl>Antiochos, S.K., Sturrock, P.A.: 1976, Influence of magnetic field structure on the conduction cooling of flare<lb/> loops. Solar Phys. 49, 359.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Antiochos, S.K., Sturrock, P.A.: 1978, Evaporative cooling of flare plasma. Astrophys. J. 220, 1137.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Antiochos, S.K., Sturrock, P.A.: 1982, The cooling and condensation of flare coronal plasma. Astrophys. J.<lb/> 254, 343.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bahcall, J.N.: 1964, Solar neutrinos. I. Theoretical. Phys. Rev. Lett. 12, 300.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bahcall, J.N.: 1989, Neutrino Astrophysics, Cambridge University Press, Cambridge.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bahcall, J.N., Davis, R. Jr.: 1976, Solar neutrinos: a scientific puzzle. Science 191, 264.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bai, T., Sturrock, P.A.: 1987, On the 152-day periodicity of the solar flare occurrence rate. Nature 327, 601.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bai, T., Sturrock, P.A.: 1989, Classification of solar flares. Annu. Rev. Astron. Astrophys. 27, 421.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bai, T., Sturrock, P.A.: 1991, The 154-day related periodicities as subharmonics of a fundamental period.<lb/> Nature 350, 141.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bai, T., Sturrock, P.A.: 1993, Evidence for a fundamental period of the sun and its relation to the 154-day<lb/> complex of periodicities. Astrophys. J. 409, 476.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Barrow, J.D.: 1998, The World Within, Oxford University Press, London, 173.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Barry, J.D.: 1981, Ball Lightning and Bead Lightning, Extreme Forms of Atmospheric Electricity, Plenum<lb/> Press, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Behe, M.J.: 1996, Darwin&apos;s Black Box: The Biochemical Challenge to Evolution, Free Press, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Behe, M.J.: 2007, The Edge of Evolution: The Search for the Limits of Darwinism, Free Press, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bell, J.S.: 1964, On the Einstein Podolsky Rosen paradox. Physics 1, 195.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Beveridge, W.I.B.: 1957, The Art of Scientific Investigation, Random House, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Bohm, D.: 1952, A suggested interpretation of the quantum theory in terms of &quot;hidden&quot; variables. Phys. Rev.<lb/> 85, 166.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Brown, S.C.: 1963, Outline of a course in plasma physics, Commission on College Physics. Am. J. Phys. 31,<lb/> 637.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Carmichael, H.: 1964, A process for flares. In: Hess, W.N.L. (ed.) The Physics of Solar Flares, NASA SP-50,<lb/> 451.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Clarke, A.C.: 1980, April OMNI, 81.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Condon, E.U., Gillmor, D.S.: 1969, Final Report of the Scientific Study of Unidentified Flying Objects, Ban-<lb/>tam, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Courant, E.D., Livingston, M.S., Snyder, H.S.: 1952, The strong-focusing synchrotron -a new high-energy<lb/> accelerator. Phys. Rev. 88, 1190.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Crick, F.H.C.: 1988, What Mad Pursuit, Basic Books, 74.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Davis, R.: 1964, Solar neutrinos. II. Experimental. Phys. Rev. Lett. 12, 303.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Dawkins, R.: 1996, The Blind Watchmaker, Norton, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Ehrenberg, W., Siday, R.E.: 1949, The refractive index in electron optics and the principles of dynamics.<lb/> Proc. Phys. Soc. B 62, 8.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Elsworth, Y., Howe, R., Isaak, G.R., McLeod, C.P., Miller, B.A., New, R., Wheeler, S.J., Gough, D.O.: 1995,<lb/> Slow rotation of the sun&apos;s interior. Nature 376, 669.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Emslie, A.G., Sturrock, P.A.: 1982, Temperature minimum heating in solar flares by resistive dissipation of<lb/> Alfven waves. Solar Phys. 80, 99.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Erber, T.: 1966, High-energy electromagnetic conversion processes in intense magnetic fields. Rev. Mod.<lb/> Phys. 38, 626.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Feinleib, M., Rogot, E., Sturrock, P.A.: 1975, Solar activity and mortality in the United States. Int. J. Epi-<lb/>demiol. 4, 227.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Finkelstein, D.: 1972, The nature of ball lightning. Phys. Today 25, 55.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Finkelstein, D., Sturrock, P.A.: 1959, Stability of high-energy plasma streams. In: Proc. Conf. Plasma Oscil-<lb/>lations, Linde Co., Indianapolis, 99.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Finkelstein, D., Sturrock, P.A.: 1961, Stability of relativistic self-focusing streams. In: Drummond, J.E. (ed.)<lb/> Plasma Physics, McGraw-Hill, New York, 224.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Fung, P.C.W., Sturrock, P.A., Switzer, P., Van Hoven, G.: 1971, Longitude distribution of solar flares. Solar<lb/> Phys. 18, 90.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Gabor, D.: 1949, Microscopy by reconstructed wavefronts. Proc. Roy. Soc. A 197, 454.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Gold, T.: 1968, Rotating neutron stars as the origin of the pulsating radio sources. Nature 218, 731.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Goldreich, P., Julian, W.: 1969, Pulsar electrodynamics. Astrophys. J. 157, 869.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hall, D.C., Sturrock, P.A.: 1967a, Stochastic magnetic pumping. Phys. Fluids 10, 1593.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hall, D.C., Sturrock, P.A.: 1967b, The diffusion, scattering and acceleration of particles by stochastic elec-<lb/>tromagnetic fields. Phys. Fluids 10, 2620.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hanbury Brown, R.: 1991, Boffin: A Personal Story of the Early Days of Radar, Radio Astronomy and Quan-<lb/>tum Optics, Hilger, Bristol, 118.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hanbury Brown, R., Twiss, R.Q.: 1956, A test of a new type of stellar interferometer on Sirius. Nature 178,<lb/> 1046.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hartle, R.E., Sturrock, P.A.: 1968, Two fluid model of the solar wind. Astrophys. J. 151, 1155.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hess, W.N. (ed.): 1964, The physics of solar flares. NASA SP-50.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hewish, A., Bell, S.J., Pilkington, J.D.H., Scott, P.F., Collins, R.A.: 1968, Observation of a rapidly pulsating<lb/> radio source. Nature 217, 709.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Hirayama, T.: 1973, Theoretical model of flares and prominences. Solar Phys. 34, 323.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Jahn, R.G.: 1992, More on mind over measurements. Phys. Today 45(3), 100.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Jahn, R.G., Colodner, P., Anderson, P.W.: 1991, A question of mind over measurements. Phys. Today 44(10),<lb/> 13.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Jenkins, J.H., Fischbach, E.: 2009, Perturbation of nuclear decay rates during the solar flare of 2006 December<lb/> 13. Astropart. Phys. 31, 407.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Jenkins, J.H., Fischbach, E., Buncher, J.B., et al.: 2009, Evidence of correlations between nuclear decay rates<lb/> and the Earth-sun distance. Astropart. Phys. 32, 42.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Kelvin, Lord: 1892, Anniversary Meeting of the Royal Society. Proc. Roy. Soc. 52, 299.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A.: 1989, Force-free magnetic fields; is there a &apos;loss of equilibrium&apos;? Astrophys.<lb/> J. 345, 1034.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A.: 1992, Three-dimensional force-free magnetic fields; flare energy buildup.<lb/> Astrophys. J. 385, 344.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A., Yang, W.-H.: 1988, Coronal magnetic fields produced by photospheric shear.<lb/> Astrophys. J. 335, 456.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Knight, J.W., Newman, C.E., Sturrock, P.A.: 1974, Two-fluid model of the solar corona. Solar Phys. 37, 183.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Knight, J.W., Sturrock, P.A.: 1976, Solar activity, geomagnetic fields, and terrestrial weather. Nature 264,<lb/> 239.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Knight, J.W., Sturrock, P.A.: 1977, Reverse current in solar flares. Astrophys. J. 318, 306.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Kopp, R.A., Pneuman, G.W.: 1976, Magnetic reconnection in the corona; the loop prominence phenomenon.<lb/> Solar Phys. 50, 85.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Lawson, J.D.: 1955, Some criteria for a power producing thermonuclear reactor. Technical Report, Atomic<lb/> Energy Research Establishment, UK.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Lipa, B.J., Sturrock, P.A., Rogot, G.: 1976, Search for correlation between geomagnetic disturbances and<lb/> mortality. Nature 259, 302.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Madey, J.J.: 1971, Stimulated emission of radiation in a periodic magnetic field. J. Appl. Phys. 42, 1906.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Meyer, S.C.: 2010, Signature in the Cell: DNA, the Evidence for Intelligent Design, Harper One, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Meyer, S.C.: 2014, Darwin&apos;s Doubt: The Explosive Origins of Animal Life, the Case for Intelligent Design,<lb/> Harper One, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Mills, D.M., Sturrock, P.A.: 1970, A model of extragalactic radio sources. Astrophys. Lett. 5, 105.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Moore, R., Porter, J., Roumeliotis, G., Tsuneta, S., Shimizu, T., Sturrock, P., et al.: 1994, Observations of<lb/> enhanced coronal heating in sheared magnetic fields. In: Proc. Symp. New Look at the Sun, Nobeyama<lb/> Radio Observatory Report 360, 89.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Newman, C.E., Sturrock, P.A.: 1969, The electrical conductivity of a collisionless magnetoplasma in a weakly<lb/> turbulent magnetic field. Phys. Fluids 12, 2553.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Newman, C.E., Sturrock, P.A., Tademaru, E.: 1971, Particle flux associated with stochastic processes. Astro-<lb/>phys. Space Sci. 10, 102.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Pantell, R.H.: 1958, Stanford University Microwave Laboratory Report ML 500.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Phillips, R.M.: 1988, History of the Ubitron. Nucl. Instrum. Methods Phys. Res., Sect. A, Accel. Spectrom.<lb/> Detect. Assoc. Equip. 272, 1.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Porter, L.J., Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A.: 1992, Cylindrically symmetric force-free magnetic fields. Astro-<lb/>phys. J. 385, 738.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Porter, L.J., Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A.: 1994a, The possible role of MHD waves in heating the solar<lb/> corona. Astrophys. J. 435, 482.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Porter, L.J., Klimchuk, J.A., Sturrock, P.A.: 1994b, The possible role of high-frequency waves in heating<lb/> solar coronal loops. Astrophys. J. 435, 502.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Rieger, E., Share, G.H., Forrest, D.J., Kanbach, G., Reppin, C., Chupp, E.L.: 1984, A 154-day periodicity in<lb/> the occurrence of hard solar flares? Nature 32, 623.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roald, C.B., Sturrock, P.A., Wolfson, R.: 1999, Coronal heating; energy release associated with chromo-<lb/>spheric magnetic reconnection. Astrophys. J. 538, 960.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roberts, D.H., Sturrock, P.A.: 1972a, The braking index and period-pulse-width distribution of pulsars. As-<lb/>trophys. J. 172, 435.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roberts, D.H., Sturrock, P.A.: 1972b, The structure of pulsar magnetospheres. Astrophys. J. Lett. 173, L3.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roberts, D.H., Turk, J.S., Sturrock, P.A.: 1973, Magnetosphere structure and the radiation mechanisms of<lb/> pulsars. Ann. N.Y. Acad. Sci. 224, 206.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roumeliotis, G.: 1996, The &quot;stress-and-relax&quot; method for reconstructing the coronal magnetic field from<lb/> vector magnetograph data. Astrophys. J. 473, 1095.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Roumeliotis, G., Sturrock, P.A., Antiochos, S.K.: 1994, A numerical study of the sudden eruption of sheared<lb/> magnetic fields. Astrophys. J. 423, 847.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Rubtsov, V.V.: 2009, The Tunguska Mystery, Springer, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Singer, S.: 1971, The Nature of Ball Lightning, Plenum Press, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Smith, D.F., Sturrock, P.A.: 1971, Maximum temperatures for radiation from plasma waves. Astrophys. Space<lb/> Sci. 12, 411.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Stenhoff, M.: 1999, Ball Lightning: An Unsolved Problem in Atmospheric Physics, Kluwer Academic, New<lb/> York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1950, Note on the focusing of electron beams in certain magnetic fields. Proc. Phys. Soc.<lb/> London B 63, 954.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1951a, The aberrations of magnetic electron lenses due to asymmetries. Phil. Trans. Roy. Soc.<lb/> London Ser. A, Math. Phys. Sci. 243, 387.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1951b, Perturbation characteristic functions and their application to electron optics. Proc. Roy.<lb/> Soc. A 210, 269.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1952, The imaging properties of electron beams in arbitrary static electromagnetic fields. Phil.<lb/> Trans. Roy. Soc. London Ser. A, Math. Phys. Sci. 245, 155.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1955, Static and Dynamic Electron Optics, Cambridge University Press, Cambridge.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1957a, An analysis of the fast-wave traveling-wave tube. Stanford University Microwave<lb/> Laboratory Report ML 469.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1957b, Nonlinear effects in electron plasmas. Proc. Roy. Soc. A 242, 277.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1958a, Nonlinear effects in alternating-gradient synchrotrons. Ann. Phys. 3, 113.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1958b, Production and focusing of high-density sheet beams. Proc. Inst. Electr. Eng.<lb/> 105B(Suppl. 12), 1032.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1958c, A variational principle for small-amplitude disturbances of electron beams. Proc. Inst.<lb/> Electr. Eng. 105B(Suppl. 11), 632.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1958d, A variational principle for small-amplitude disturbances of electron beams and of<lb/> electron-ion plasmas. Ann. Phys. 4, 306.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1958e, Kinematics of growing waves. Phys. Rev. 112, 1488.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1959a, Theory of focusing of sheet beams in periodic fields. J. Electron. Control 7, 153.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1959b, Magnetic deflection focusing. J. Electron. Control 7, 162.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1960a, Balanced acceleration and deflection electrostatic focusing. J. Electron. Control 8,<lb/> 267.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1960b, Action transfer and frequency-shift relations in the nonlinear theory of waves and<lb/> oscillations. Ann. Phys. 9, 422.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1960c, In what sense do slow waves carry negative energy? J. Appl. Phys. 31, 2052.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1961, Nonlinear effects in electron plasmas. J. Nucl. Energy, Part C Plasma Phys. 2, 158.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1964, Nonlinear theory of electrostatic waves in plasmas. In: Rosenbluth, M.N. (ed.) Enrico<lb/> Fermi International School of Physics, Academic Press, London, 180.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1965, Galactic flares and quasi-stellar radio sources. Nature 205, 861.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1966a, Model of the high energy phase of solar flares. Nature 211, 695.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1966b, A model of quasi-stellar radio sources. Nature 211, 697.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1968, A model of solar flares. In: Kiepenheuer, K.O. (ed.) Structure and Development of Solar<lb/> Active Regions, Reidel, Dordrecht, 471.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1970a, Pulsar radiation mechanisms. Nature 227, 465.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1970b, On the possibility of accretion by quasi-stellar objects. Astrophys. J. Lett. 159, L139.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1971a, A model of pulsars. Astrophys. J. 164, 529.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1971b, The period-age distribution of pulsars. Astrophys. J. Lett. 169, L7.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1971c, On the possibility of pulsar action in quasars. Astrophys. J. 170, 85.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1973, Evaluation of astrophysical hypotheses. Astrophys. J. 182, 569.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1985, Extragalactic variable radio sources. Astrophys. J. 293, 52.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1994a, Introduction to Plasma Physics, Cambridge University Press, Cambridge.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1994b, Applied scientific inference, J. Sci. Explor. 8, 491.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1994c, Report on a survey of the membership of the American astronomical society concern-<lb/>ing the UFO problem: part 1. J. Sci. Explor. 8, 1.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1994d, Report on a survey of the membership of the American astronomical society concern-<lb/>ing the UFO problem: part 2. J. Sci. Explor. 8, 153.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1994e, Report on a survey of the membership of the American astronomical society concern-<lb/>ing the UFO problem: part 3. J. Sci. Explor. 8, 309.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1999a, Chromospheric magnetic reconnection and its possible relationship to coronal heating.<lb/> Astrophys. J. 521, 451.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 1999b, The UFO Enigma: A New Review of the Physical Evidence, Warner Books, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 2009, A Tale of Two Sciences, Memoirs of a Dissident Scientist, Exoscience, Palo Alto.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 2013, AKA Shakespeare, a Scientific Approach to the Authorship Question, Exoscience, Palo<lb/> Alto.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 2015, Late Night Thoughts About Science, Exoscience, Palo Alto.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A.: 2016, A Conjecture Concerning Ball Lightning. arXiv.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Aschwanden, M.: 2012, Flares in the crab nebula driven by untwisting magnetic field. Astro-<lb/>phys. J. Lett. 751, L32.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Bai, T.: 1992, Search for evidence of a clock related to the solar 154-day complex of period-<lb/>icities. Astrophys. J. 397, 337.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Baker, K.B.: 1979, Positron production by pulsars. Astrophys. J. 234, 612.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Barbosa, D.: 1978, The exterior source surface for force-free fields. Astron. Astrophys. 62,<lb/> 267.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Barnes, C.W.: 1972a, Force-free magnetic-field structures and their role in solar activity. As-<lb/>trophys. J. 174, 659.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Barnes, C.W.: 1972b, Activity in galaxies and quasars. Astrophys. J. 176, 31.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Coppi, B.: 1964, A new model of solar flares. Nature 204, 61.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Coppi, B.: 1966, A new model of solar flares. Astrophys. J. 143, 3.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Feldman, P.A.: 1968a, A mechanism for quasar continuum radiation and its possible applica-<lb/>tion to Seyfert nuclei. Astron. J. 73, 910.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Feldman, P.A.: 1968b, A mechanism for continuum radiation from quasi-stellar radio sources<lb/> with application to 3C 273B. Astrophys. J. Lett. 152, L39.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Groves, T.R.: 2010, More variations on Aharonov-Bohm. Phys. Today 63(4), 8.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Hartle, R.D.: 1966, Two-fluid model of the solar wind. Phys. Rev. Lett. 16, 628.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Moore, R.L.: 1969, A mechanism for pulsar radio emission. Bull. Am. Astron. Soc. 1, 206.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Petrosian, V.: 1973, Impulsive solar X-ray bursts; bremsstrahlung radiation from a beam of<lb/> electrons in the solar chromosphere and the total energy of solar flares. Astrophys. J. 186, 291.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Roberts, D.H.: 1973, Pulsar magnetospheres, braking index, polar caps, and period-pulse-<lb/>width distributions. Astrophys. J. 181, 161.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Scargle, J.D.: 2006, Power-spectrum analysis of Super-Kamiokande solar neutrino data, taking<lb/> into account asymmetry in the error estimate. Solar Phys. 237, 1.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Uchida, Y.: 1981, Coronal heating by stochastic magnetic pumping. Astrophys. J. 246, 331.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Antiochos, S.K., Roumeliotis, G.: 1995, Asymptotic analysis of force-free magnetic fields of<lb/> cylindrical symmetry. Astrophys. J. 443, 804.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Baker, K.B., Turk, J.S.: 1976, Pulsar extinction. Astrophys. J. 206, 273.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Ball, R.H., Baldwin, D.E.: 1965, Radiation at the plasma frequency and its harmonic from a<lb/> turbulent plasma. Phys. Fluids 8, 1509.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Fung, P.C.W., Smith, D.F.: 1971, A weak turbulence analysis of the two-stream instability. J.<lb/> Plasma Phys. 5, 11.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Harding, A.K., Daugherty, J.K.: 1989, Cascade model of gamma-ray bursts. Astrophys. J. 346,<lb/> 950.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Kaufmann, P., Smith, D.F.: 1985, Energy release in solar flares; unstable current systems and<lb/> plasma instabilities in astrophysics. In: Kundu, M.R., Holman, G.D. (eds.) Proc. IAU Symp. 107, Reidel,<lb/> Dordrecht, 293.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Petrosian, V., Turk, J.S.: 1975, Optical radiation from the crab pulsar. Astrophys. J. 196, 73.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Roald, C.B., Wolfson, R.: 1999, Chromospheric magnetic reconnection and its implications<lb/> for coronal heating. Astrophys. J. Lett. 524, L75.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Steinitz, G., Fischbach, E.: 2017, Analysis of Radon-Chain Decay Measurements: Evidence<lb/> of Solar Influences and Inferences Concerning Solar Internal Structure and the Role of Neutrinos. arXiv.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Walther, G., Wheatland, M.S.: 1997, Search for periodicities in the Homestake solar neutrino<lb/> data. Astrophys. J. 491, 409.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Wheatland, M.S., Acton, L.W.: 1996, Yohkoh soft X-ray telescope images of the diffuse solar<lb/> corona. Astrophys. J. Lett. 461, 115.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., et al.: 1966, Report of panel to discuss teaching of plasma physics in American universities.<lb/> Am. J. Phys. 34, 104.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Kaufmann, P., Moore, R.L., Smith, D.F.: 1984, Energy release in solar flares. Solar Phys. 94,<lb/> 341.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Dixon, W.W., Klimchuk, J.A., Antiochos, S.K.: 1990, Episodic coronal heating. Astrophys. J.<lb/> Lett. 356, L31.<lb/> </bibl>
        P.A. Sturrock<lb/> 
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Antiochos, S.K., Klimchuk, J.A., Roumeliotis, G.: 1994a, Asymptotic forms for the energy of<lb/> force-free magnetic-field configurations of translational symmetry. Astrophys. J. 431, 870.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Klimchuk, J.A., Roumeliotis, G., Antiochos, S.K.: 1994b, The asymptotic behavior of force-<lb/>free magnetic-field configurations. In: Balasubramaniam, K.S., Simon, G.W. (eds.) Solar Active Region<lb/> Evolution, Comparing Models with Observations, ASP Conf. Series 68, 219.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Weber, M.A., Wheatland, M.S., Wolfson, R.: 2001, Metastable magnetic configurations their<lb/> significance for solar eruptive events. Astrophys. J. 548, 492.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Buncher, J.B., Fischbach, E., Gruenwald, J.T., Javorsek, D. II, Jenkins, J.H., et al.: 2010a,<lb/> Power spectrum analysis of BNL decay rate data. Astropart. Phys. 34, 121.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Buncher, J.B., Fischbach, E., Gruenwald, J.T., Javorsek, D. II, Jenkins, J.H., et al.: 2010b,<lb/> Power spectrum analysis of Physikalisch-Technisch Bundesanstalt decay-rate data: evidence for solar<lb/> rotational modulation. Solar Phys. 267, 251.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Buncher, J.B., Fischbach, E., Javorsek, D. II, Jenkins, J.H., Mattes, J.J.: 2011, Concerning the<lb/> phases of the annual variations of nuclear decay rates. Astrophys. J. 737, 65.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Steinitz, G., Fischbach, E., Javorsek, D. II, Jenkins, J.H.: 2012, Analysis of gamma radiation<lb/> from a Radon source: indications of a solar influence. Astropart. Phys. 36, 18.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Sturrock, P.A., Fischbach, E., Javorsek, D. II, Jenkins, J.H., Lee, R.H.: 2013, The case for a solar influence on<lb/> certain nuclear decay rates. In: Contributed to the 8th Patras Workshop on Axions, WIMPs and WISPs,<lb/> Chicago, July 18-22, 2012. arXiv.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Tavani, M., Bulgarelli, A., Vittorino, V., Pellizoni, A., Striani, E., Caraveo, P., et al.: 2011, Discovery of<lb/> powerful gamma-ray flares from the crab nebula. Science 331, 736.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Thompson, W.B.: 1964, An Introduction to Plasma Physics, Pergamon Press, Elmsford.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Townes, C.H.: 1999, How the Laser Happened, Oxford University Press, London, 42.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Watson, J.D.: 1996, The Double Helix -A Personal Account of the Discovery of the Structure of DNA, Simon<lb/> and Schuster, New York.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Wheatland, M.S., Sturrock, P.A.: 1996, Avalanche models of solar flares; the distribution of active regions.<lb/> Astrophys. J. 471, 1044.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Wheatland, M.S., Sturrock, P.A., Acton, L.W.: 1997, Coronal heating; the vertical temperature structure of<lb/> the quiet corona. Astrophys. J. 482, 510.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Wheatland, M.S., Sturrock, P.A., McTiernan, J.: 1998, The waiting-time distribution of solar flare hard X-ray<lb/> bursts. Astrophys. J. 509, 448.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Wheatland, M.S., Sturrock, P.A., Roumeliotis, G.: 2000, An optimization approach to reconstructing force-<lb/>free fields. Astrophys. J. 540, 1150.<lb/> </bibl>
        <bibl>Yang, W.H., Sturrock, P.A., Antiochos, S.K.: 1986, Force-free magnetic fields; the magneto-frictional method.<lb/> Astrophys. J. 309, 383.</bibl>
        </listBibl>
    </text>
</tei>

